A Guide to the Papers of Henry Evans Howell, Jr. 1948-1976
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University Libraries, Old Dominion University
- Political Papers 1948-1973
  - Sub-Series K: 1970-1971 General Correspondence
    - Joe Fitzpatrick Congressional Race; Correspondence; Campaign Materials, April-November, 1970 (Box-folder Box 82 Folder 11)
    - George Rawlings U.S. Senate Race; General Correspondence, January-October, 1970 (Box-folder Box 82 Folder 12)
    - Campaign Materials, 1970 (Box-folder Box 82 Folder 13)
    - Expenditures - Norfolk Area, 1970-1971 (Box-folder Box 82 Folder 14)
    - Expenditures - Norfolk Area; Payments to Campaign Workers, 1970 (Box-folder Box 82 Folder 15)
    - Finances - Bank Account Records, Norfolk Committee, 1970-1971 (Box-folder Box 82 Folder 16)
    - Finances - Correspondence re: Norfolk Campaign, 1970-1971 (Box-folder Box 83 Folder 1)
    - Finances - Fitzpatrick and Rawlings Fundraiser, October 20, 1970 (Box-folder Box 83 Folder 2)
    - News Releases, 1970 (Box-folder Box 83 Folder 3)
    - Organization - "Get Out the Vote" Campaign among Blacks, October-November, 1970 Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box-folder Box 83 Folder 4)
    - Watkins M. Abbitt - Henry Howell (Box-folder Box 83 Folder 5)
    - A. Linwood Holton - Henry Howell (Box-folder Box 83 Folder 6)
    - Andrew P. Miller - Henry Howell (Box-folder Box 83 Folder 7)
    - J. Sargeant Reynolds - Henry Howell (Box-folder Box 83 Folder 8)
    - William B. Spong, Jr. - Henry Howell (Box-folder Box 83 Folder 9)
    - G. William Whitehurst - Henry Howell (Box-folder Box 83 Folder 10)
    - Henry Howell - Norfolk Members of General Assembly (Box-folder Box 83 Folder 11)
    - Henry Howell - Norfolk City Officials (Box-folder Box 83 Folder 12)
    - Henry Howell - Political Allies (Box-folder Box 83 Folder 13)
    - Henry Howell Correspondence during the 1970 George Rawlings' U.S. Senate Race (Box-folder Box 83 Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, January-February, 1971 (Box-folder Box 83 Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, March-April, 1971 (Box-folder Box 83 Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, May-June, 1971 (Box-folder Box 83 Folder 17)
    - Howell News Releases (Mostly Speeches) March-May, 1971 (Box-folder Box 83 Folder 18)
    - Howell News Releases (Mostly Speeches) June-July, 1971 (Box-folder Box 83 Folder 19)
    - Bob Brown correspondence; Virginia Young Democrats, 1970-1971 (Box-folder Box 83 Folder 20)
    - Fundraising: Use of Bank Americard and Master Charge, 1970 (Box-folder Box 83 Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series L: 1973 Gubernatorial Campaign
    - General Correspondence, July-September, 1971 (Box-folder Box 84 Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, October-November, 1971 (Box-folder Box 84 Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence (First District), July-August, 1971 (Box-folder Box 84 Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence (Chesapeake), July-August, 1971 (Box-folder Box 84 Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence (Norfolk), July-August, 1971 (Box-folder Box 84 Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence (Portsmouth), July-August, 1971 (Box-folder Box 84 Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence (Virginia Beach), July-October, 1971 (Box-folder Box 84 Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence (Richmond and 3rd District), July-August, 1971 (Box-folder Box 84 Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence (4th District), July-August, 1971 (Box-folder Box 84 Folder 9)
    - General Correspondence (5th District), July-August, 1971 (Box-folder Box 84 Folder 10)
    - General Correspondence (6th District), July-September, 1971 (Box-folder Box 84 Folder 11)
    - General Correspondence (7th District), July-August, 1971 (Box-folder Box 84 Folder 12)
    - General Correspondence (8th District), July-October, 1971 (Box-folder Box 84 Folder 13)
    - General Correspondence (9th District), October-November, 1971 (Box-folder Box 84 Folder 14)
    - General Correspondence (No. Virginia: 10th District and Part of 8th), June-October, 1971 (Box-folder Box 84 Folder 15)
    - General Correspondence (Out of State), June-September, 1971 (Box-folder Box 84 Folder 16)
    - General Correspondence: Nominating Petitions, July-August, 1971 (Box-folder Box 84 Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Miscellaneous Questionnaires, Responses to Same, September-October, 1971 (Box-folder Box 84 Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Letters re: VEPCO Rate Increase Demands, August-September, 1971 (Box-folder Box 84 Folder 19)
    - Anti-Howell Correspondence, July-November, 1971 (Box-folder Box 84 Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Thank You Letters to Campaign Workers, November 1971 (Box-folder Box 84 Folder 21)
    - Congratulatory Letters from Political Figures, November 1971 (Box-folder Box 85 Folder 1)
    - Congratulatory Telegrams, November-December, 1917 (Box-folder Box 85 Folder 2)
    - Congratulatory Letters, November 3, 1971 (Box-folder Box 85 Folder 3)
    - Congratulatory Letters, November 3, 1971 (Box-folder Box 85 Folder 4)
    - Congratulatory Letters, November 4, 1971 (Box-folder Box 85 Folder 5)
    - Congratulatory Letters, November 5, 1971 (Box-folder Box 85 Folder 6)
    - Congratulatory Letters, November 6-9, 1971 (Box-folder Box 85 Folder 7)
    - Congratulatory Letters, November 10 - December 1, 1971 (Box-folder Box 85 Folder 8)
    - Bumper Stickers; Tickets, 1971 (Box-folder Box 85 Folder 9)
    - Form Letters, 1971 (Box-folder Box 85 Folder 10)
    - Undelivered Campaign Mail, August-November, 1971 (Box-folder Box 85 Folder 11)
    - Forms; Stationery, 1971 (Box-folder Box 86 Folder 1)
    - Pamphlets; Flyers, 1971 (Box-folder Box 86 Folder 2)
    - Sample Guide Ballots, 1971 (Box-folder Box 86 Folder 3)
    - Election Returns, November 1971 (Box-folder Box 86 Folder 4)
    - Expenses re: "Get Out the Vote" Effort, October 1971 (Box-folder Box 86 Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence re: Fundraising, August-October, 1971 (Box-folder Box 86 Folder 6)
    - Buck Books - Records for So. Tidewater, 1971 (Box-folder Box 86 Folder 7)
    - Buck Books - Statewide Records, 1971 (Box-folder Box 86 Folder 8)
    - Buck Books - Miscellaneous Records, 1971 (Box-folder Box 86 Folder 9)
    - Buck Books, Sample - 1969, 1971 (Box-folder Box 86 Folder 10)
    - Contributions - Records from 1969 and 1971 (Box-folder Box 86 Folder 11)
    - Contributions - Records re: 1971 (Box-folder Box 86 Folder 12)
    - In-kind Contributions - Free Hotel Accommodations, August 1971 (Box-folder Box 86 Folder 13)
    - Contributors to 1970 George Rawlings Campaign, October 1971 (Box-folder Box 86 Folder 14)
    - Contributors (Jewish) to 1969 Campaign (Box-folder Box 86 Folder 15)
    - Fundraising Picnic in Virginia Beach, September 26, 1971 (Box-folder Box 86 Folder 16)
    - Fundraising Picnic (9/26) - Lists of Ticket Holders, September 26, 1971 (Box-folder Box 86 Folder 17)
    - Labor, General Correspondence, September-November, 1971 (Box-folder Box 86 Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Lists, 1971 (Box-folder Box 86 Folder 19)
    - Correspondence re: Financial Contributions, August-November, 1971 (Box-folder Box 86 Folder 20)
    - Records re: Financial Contributions in 1969 (Box-folder Box 87 Folder 1)
    - Mailing Lists, Norfolk Area (Miscellaneous), 1971 (Box-folder Box 87 Folder 2)
    - Guest Booking - Opening of No. Virginia Headquarters, 1971 (Box-folder Box 87 Folder 3)
    - People Invited to Hear I.R.A. Poll Results, July 2G, 1971 (Box-folder Box 87 Folder 4)
    - News Releases, Miscellaneous Rough Drafts, 1971 (Box-folder Box 87 Folder 5)
    - Material for Preparing Releases on Busing, August - October, 1971 (Box-folder Box 87 Folder 6)
    - News Releases, Prior to Announcement, July 1971 (Box-folder Box 87 Folder 7)
    - News Releases, Nos. 1-10, July 27 - September 6, 1971 (Box-folder Box 87 Folder 8)
    - News Releases, Nos. 11-20, September 6-17, 1971 (Box-folder Box 87 Folder 9)
    - News Releases, Nos. 21-30, September 18-25, 1971 (Box-folder Box 87 Folder 10)
    - News Releases, Nos. 31-40, October 2-16, 1971 (Box-folder Box 87 Folder 11)
    - News Releases, Nos. 41-50, October 17-27, 1971 (Box-folder Box 87 Folder 12)
    - News Releases, Nos. 51-56, October 28 - November 2, 1971 (Box-folder Box 87 Folder 13)
    - Materials for Precinct Work, 1971 (Box-folder Box 87 Folder 14)
    - Distributing Guide Ballots (Records), October 1971 (Box-folder Box 87 Folder 15)
    - Instructions for Phoners; Election Day Workers, 1971 (Box-folder Box 87 Folder 16)
    - Organization (Local) First District, 1971 (Box-folder Box 88 Folder 1)
    - Organization (Local) Second District, 1971 (Box-folder Box 88 Folder 2)
    - Organization (Local) Third District, 1971 (Box-folder Box 88 Folder 3)
    - Organization (Local) Fourth District, 1971 (Box-folder Box 88 Folder 4)
    - Organization (Local) Fifth District, 1971 (Box-folder Box 88 Folder 5)
    - Organization (Local) Sixth District, 1971 (Box-folder Box 88 Folder 6)
    - Organization (Local) Seventh District, 1971 (Box-folder Box 88 Folder 7)
    - Organization (Local) Eighth District, 1971 (Box-folder Box 88 Folder 8)
    - Organization (Local) Ninth District, 1971 (Box-folder Box 88 Folder 9)
    - Organization (Local) Chesapeake, 1971 (Box-folder Box 88 Folder 10)
    - Correspondence re: Office Equipment, 1971 (Box-folder Box 88 Folder 11)
    - Requests for Personal Appearances and Related Correspondence, August-October, 1971 (Box-folder Box 88 Folder 12)
    - Issues for No. Virginia Campaign, 1971 (Box-folder Box 88 Folder 13)
    - County Registrars, List, 1971 (Box-folder Box 88 Folder 14)
    - Issues - Miscellaneous Material (Alphabetical), 1971 (Box-folder Box 88 Folder 15)
    - Kostel Campaign (Democratic Candidate), 1971 (Box-folder Box 88 Folder 16)
    - Norfolk, City of (Roster and Directory), 1971 (Box-folder Box 88 Folder 17)
    - Shafron Campaign (Republican Candidate), 1971 (Box-folder Box 88 Folder 18)
    - Virginia - Miscellaneous Material, 1971 (Box-folder Box 88 Folder 19)
    - Howell Private Schedule (Incomplete), September 1971 (Box-folder Box 88 Folder 20)
    - Howell Private Schedule, October-November, 1971 (Box-folder Box 89 Folder 1)
    - Public Schedules (Incomplete), September-October, 1971 (Box-folder Box 89 Folder 2)
    - Betty Howell Schedules, October 1971 (Box-folder Box 89 Folder 3)
    - Schedule Requests Forms (Completed) - No Decision Taken, September- October, 1971 (Box-folder Box 89 Folder 4)
    - Personal Appearances Scheduled, July-October, 1971 (Box-folder Box 89 Folder 5)
    - Requests for Personal Appearances turned Down, July-November, 1971 (Box-folder Box 89 Folder 6)
    - Media Campaign: Correspondence with Lois Holland Calloway, September-October, 1971 (Box-folder Box 89 Folder 7)
    - Polling - IRA Poll, June-September, 1971 (Box-folder Box 89 Folder 8)
    - Press Coverage - Correspondence; Plans, 1971 (Box-folder Box 89 Folder 9)
    - Radio Ads - Beeper System, 1971 (Box-folder Box 89 Folder 10)
    - Radio Spots (Proposed Ads for 9th District), 1971 (Box-folder Box 89 Folder 11)
    - T.V. Ads - Copy; Schedules, 1971 (Box-folder Box 89 Folder 12)
    - T.V. and Radio Interviews, August-October, 1971 (Box-folder Box 89 Folder 13)
    - Lists of Volunteer Workers - Tidewater Area, 1971 (Box-folder Box 89 Folder 14)
    - Volunteer Workers from Previous Campaigns, 1971 (Box-folder Box 89 Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Lists of Potential Campaign Workers, 1971 (Box-folder Box 89 Folder 16)
    - Lists of Campaign Workers Invited to Inauguration, November-December, 1971 (Box-folder Box 89 Folder 17)
    - February-May, 1973 (Box-folder Box 90 Folder 1)
    - June 1973 (Box-folder Box 90 Folder 2)
    - July-August, 1973 (Box-folder Box 90 Folder 3)
    - September-November, 1973 (Box-folder Box 90 Folder 4)
    - (Newsclippings Attached), July-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 90 Folder 5)
    - Periodicals, Newsletters, February-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 90 Folder 6)
    - First District, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 90 Folder 7)
    - First District (Hampton, Newport News), 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 90 Folder 8)
    - Second District (Norfolk), 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 90 Folder 9)
    - Second District (Virginia Beach), 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 90 Folder 10)
    - Third District, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 90 Folder 11)
    - Fourth District (General; Portsmouth; Chesapeake), 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 90 Folder 12)
    - Fifth District (General; Martinsville - Danville), 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 90 Folder 13)
    - Sixth District (Roanoke; General), 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 90 Folder 14)
    - Seventh District (Charlottesville; General), 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 90 Folder 15)
    - Ninth District, 1972 (Box-folder Box 90 Folder 16)
    - Ninth District, 1973 Box 91 (Box-folder Box 90 Folder 17)
    - No. Virginia (8th District; Alexandria; Arlington), 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 91 Folder 1)
    - No. Virginia (10th District), 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 91 Folder 2)
    - Out of State, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 91 Folder 3)
    - Announcement Rally, April 7, 1973 (Box-folder Box 91 Folder 4)
    - Announcement Rally, April 7, 1973 (Box-folder Box 91 Folder 5)
    - Howell Thank You's re: People's Rally, April 7, 1973 (Box-folder Box 91 Folder 6)
    - Letters from Active Howell Supporters, December 1972-March 1973 (Box-folder Box 91 Folder 7)
    - Letters from Active Howell Supporters, April-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 91 Folder 8)
    - Correspondence with Active Supporters, December 1972 - March 1973 (Box-folder Box 91 Folder 9)
    - Correspondence with Active Supporters, April-June, 1973 (Box-folder Box 91 Folder 10)
    - Correspondence with Active Supporters, July-August, 1973 (Box-folder Box 91 Folder 11)
    - Correspondence with Active Supporters, September-November, 1973 (Box-folder Box 91 Folder 12)
    - Correspondence with Verbal Supporters, January-June, 1973 (Box-folder Box 91 Folder 13)
    - Correspondence with Verbal Supporters, July-August, 1973 (Box-folder Box 91 Folder 14)
    - Correspondence with Verbal Supporters, September-November, 1973 (Box-folder Box 91Folder 15)
    - HEH Appeals to Former Supporters, 1973 (Box-folder Box 91 Folder 16)
    - Anti-Howell Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 1)
    - Constituent Letters - Samples, 1970-1972 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 2)
    - Henry Howell - Jimmy Carter Correspondence, 1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 3)
    - Henry Howell - Mills Godwin Correspondence, 1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 4)
    - Henry Howell - Mrs. Robert Kennedy, June 1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 5)
    - Henry Howell - Sydney and Frances Lewis, March-August, 1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 6)
    - Correspondence with Democratic Local Committees re: Candidacy, January-February, 1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 7)
    - League of Women Voters, 1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 8)
    - Young Democrats (Statewide, Local), 1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 9)
    - Correspondence re: "Fair Practices," September 1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 10)
    - Correspondence re: Mental Hospitals in Virginia, September 1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 11)
    - Correspondence re: Utilities, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 12)
    - Betty Howell Correspondence, 1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 13)
    - Staff Correspondence; Rey Barry, February 1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 14)
    - Staff Correspondence: Karen Doty, June-July, 1973 Correspondence: Elyce Fishman, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 15)
    - Staff Correspondence: Jerry Fitzgerald, September 1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 17)
    - Staff Correspondence: John Greenbacker, May-September, 1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 18)
    - Staff Correspondence: Henry McLaughlin (Press Headquarters - Richmond), February-May, 1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 19)
    - Staff Correspondence: Henry McLaughlin (Press Headquarters - Richmond), June-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 20)
    - Staff Correspondence: Henry McLaughlin, March-September, 1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 21)
    - Staff Correspondence: Henry McLaughlin, 1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 22)
    - Staff Correspondence: Miscellaneous, February-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 23)
    - Staff Correspondence: Howell Press Headquarters (Richmond), April-June, 1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 24)
    - Staff Correspondence: Howell Press Headquarters (Richmond), July-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 25)
    - Staff Correspondence: Karen Sichta, May-August, 1973 (Box-folder Box 92 Folder 26)
    - Staff Correspondence: Chris Spanos, January-May,1973 (Box-folder Box 93 Folder 1)
    - Staff: Chris Spanos, June 1973 (Box-folder Box 93 Folder 2)
    - Staff: Chris Spanos, July-August, 1973 (Box-folder Box 93 Folder 3)
    - Staff: Chris Spanos, September-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 93 Folder 4)
    - Memos to Henry Howell from Miscellaneous Staff Members, February-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 93 Folder 5)
    - Memos from HEH to Campaign Staff, August-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 93 Folder 6)
    - Henry Howell - Chuck Baker, April-May, 1973 (Box-folder Box 93 Folder 7)
    - Henry Howell - Zack Clements, August 1973 (Box-folder Box 93 Folder 8)
    - Henry Howell - Elyce Fishman, fall 1972, February 1973 (Box-folder Box 93 Folder 9)
    - Henry Howell - Elyce Fishman, March-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 93 Folder 10)
    - Henry Howell - Jim Gibbs, February-August, 1973 (Box-folder Box 93 Folder11)
    - Henry Howell - Henry McLaughlin, February- October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 93 Folder 12)
    - Henry Howell - Chris Spanos, December 1972- October 1973 (Box-folder Box 93 Folder 13)
    - HEH - George Tyler (Issues Group), 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 94 Folder 1)
    - Intra-Staff Memos, January-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 94 Folder 2)
    - Catherine J. Crane (Campaign Treasurer) - Memos To and From, January-November, 1973 (Box-folder Box 94 Folder 3)
    - Elyce Fishman - Memos To and From, February-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 94 Folder 4)
    - Elyce Fishman - Henry McLaughlin, May-September, 1973 (Box-folder Box 94 Folder 5)
    - Elyce Fishman - Chris Spanos, March-September, 1973 (Box-folder Box 94 Folder 6)
    - Jim Gibbs - Memos To and From, April-September, 1973 (Box-folder Box 94 Folder 7)
    - Memos from Henry McLaughlin, April-September, 1973 (Box-folder Box 94 Folder 8)
    - Memos to Henry McLaughlin, April-June, 1973 (Box-folder Box 94 Folder 9)
    - Henry McLaughlin - Jim Gibbs, April-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 94 Folder 10)
    - Memos from Chris Spanos, March-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 94 Folder 11)
    - Memos to Chris Spanos, April-November, 1973 (Box-folder Box 94 Folder 12)
    - Chris Spanos - Howard Copeland, July-September, 1973 (Box-folder Box 94 Folder 13)
    - Chris Spanos - Henry McLaughlin, March-September, 1973 (Box-folder Box 94 Folder 14)
    - Memos of various Staff Members, February-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 94 Folder 15)
    - Intra-Staff: ABC Tax Plan - Businessmen's Statement, October 1973 (Box-folder Box 94 Folder 16)
    - Intra-Staff: ABC Tax Plan - Correspondence re: Surrogates, September-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 94 Folder 17)
    - Campaign Issues, November 1971 - July 1973 (Box-folder Box 94 Folder 18)
    - Campaign Issues, August-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 94 Folder 19)
    - Campaign Materials, June-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 95 Folder 1)
    - Campaign Organization, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 95 Folder 2)
    - COMPAC Form Letters, April-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 95 Folder 3)
    - Correspondence re: "Fair Practices," September, 1973 (Box-folder Box 95 Folder 4)
    - Field Operations (Local Campaigning), June-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 95 Folder 5)
    - "Front Lash," May 1973 (Box-folder Box 95 Folder 6)
    - Howell Announcement Rally, April 7, 1973 (Box-folder Box 95 Folder 7)
    - Howell Announcement Rally, April 7, 1973 (Box-folder Box 95 Folder 8)
    - Local Campaigning - Miscellaneous Material, 1973 (Box-folder Box 95 Folder 9)
    - Local Campaigning (First District), January-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 95 Folder 10)
    - Local Campaigning (Second District), 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 95 Folder 11)
    - Local Campaigning (Third District), 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 95 Folder 12)
    - Local Campaigning (Fourth District, Portsmouth), 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 95 Folder 13)
    - Local Campaigning (Fifth District), January-June, 1973 (Box-folder Box 95 Folder 14)
    - Local Campaigning (Fifth District), July-November, 1973 (Box-folder Box 95 Folder 15)
    - Local Campaigning (Sixth District), 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 95 Folder 16)
    - Local Campaigning (Seventh District), 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 95 Folder 17)
    - Local Campaigning (Ninth District), 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 96 Folder 1)
    - Local Campaigning (No. Virginia) Eighth and Tenth Districts, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 96 Folder 2)
    - Media Campaign, March-November, 1973 (Box-folder Box 96 Folder 3)
    - Media - A.V. Presentations at County Fairs, August 1973 (Box-folder Box 96 Folder 4)
    - Media - Campaign Song "Howell Cannonball," 1973 (Box-folder Box 96 Folder 5)
    - Media - Premiere of Howell Campaign Film, September-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 96 Folder 6)
    - Media - Press Campaign, January-May, 1973 (Box-folder Box 96 Folder 7)
    - Media - Press Campaign, June-November, 1973 (Box-folder Box 96 Folder 8)
    - Media - Radio Campaign, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 96 Folder 9)
    - Media - T.V. Campaign, February-November, 1973 (Box-folder Box 96 Folder 10)
    - Personnel, 1973 (Box-folder Box 96 Folder 11)
    - Personnel - Hiring a Campaign Manager, December 1972- March 1973 (Box-folder Box 96 Folder 12)
    - Personnel - Hiring Campaign Workers, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 96 Folder 13)
    - Phone Calls, April-July, 1973 (Box-folder Box 96 Folder 14)
    - Scheduling Memos, April-July, 1973 (Box-folder Box 96 Folder 15)
    - Scheduling Memos, August-November, 1973 (Box-folder Box 97 Folder 1)
    - Virginia Common Cause, June & October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 97 Folder 2)
    - Virginia Democratic Party, March-May, 1973 (Box-folder Box 97 Folder 3)
    - George Wallace (Use of), August-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 97 Folder 4)
    - Youth Activities (Students), 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 97 Folder 5)
    - Black Support, Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 97 Folder 6)
    - Black Support, Staff Correspondence (especially J. Allen Ball), 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 97 Folder 7)
    - Lists of Black Leaders, 1973 (Box-folder Box 97 Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, January-October, 1973 (Box-folder Box 97 Folder 9)
    - Biographies of Henry Howell, 1973 (Box-folder Box 97 Folder 10)
    - "Henry" - Rey Barry, 1973 (Box-folder Box 97 Folder 11)
    - Biography of Betty Howell, 1973 (Box-folder Box 97 Folder 12)
    - "Henry Howell on the Issues," 1973 (Box-folder Box 97 Folder 13)
    - Howell Legislative Goals, 1971 (Box-folder Box 97 Folder 14)
    - "Plain Talk" - Howell Newspaper, 1973 (Box-folder Box 97 Folder 15)
    - Howell Platform, 1973 (Box-folder Box 97 Folder 16)
    - HEH Robo Letters (Form Letters), 1973 (Box-folder Box 97 Folder 17)
    - Position Papers (Alphabetical), 1973 (Box-folder Box 98 Folder 1)
    - Rough Drafts for Literature, 1973 (Box-folder Box 98 Folder 2)
    - Position Papers (Rough Drafts), 1973 (Box-folder Box 98 Folder 3)
    - Rough Drafts by Don Lago, December 1972 (Box-folder Box 98 Folder 4)
    - Samples (I), 1973 (Box-folder Box 98 Folder 5)
    - Samples (II), 1973 (Box-folder Box 98 Folder 6)
    - Speeches, Drafts of Speeches and Statements re: A.B.C. Tax Plan, 1973 (Box-folder Box 98 Folder 7)
    - Speeches - Rough Draft of Industrial Development Speech, August 1973 (Box-folder Box 98 Folder 8)
    - Speeches - Miscellaneous Rough Drafts, 1973 (Box-folder Box 98 Folder 9)